

#### **ABOUT ME**

My area of expertise lies in Business Intelligence and Data Analytics. I consistently strive to enhance my knowledge and skills in these fields. I am renowned for my proficiency in solving complex problems through an analytical and creative approach, enabling me to arrive at optimal and logical solutions efficiently.

#### **CONTACT INFORMATION**

Address: Bogotá, Colombia

Cell: 3134800647

Email: moneijuan@gmail.com

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/juan-david-

mosquera-neira

## **LANGUAGES**

Spanish: Native

English: Intermediate

# **PROGRAMS**

- EXCEL
- POWER BI
- TABLEAU
- HTML-CSS
- ALTERYX
- SQL SERVER
- PYTHON
- AZURE



# **PORTFOLIO**

Link: Pending

# JUAN MOSQUERA

# DATA ANALYST

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Data Analytics**

Mediabrands, dic 2022 - Present

- · Create databases using SQL Server for new clients.
- Responsible for updating daily databases using Python to download and store in SQL Server.
- Design and develop interactive and visually appealing dashboards using tools such as Tableau.
- Develop ELT processes with Alteryx tool.

#### **Assoc Solution Consultant**

ACI Worldwide, feb 2022 - dic 2022

- Create tools to optimize the time and quality of the consultant's interactions both internally and with the end customer.
- Perform tracking reports, corporate CRM dashboards and dashboard development.
- Document analysis and entry strategies for new payment industry segments.
- Support the consultant's daily work with specific documents upon request for opportunities, specific tasks that enable positioning and market opening.

### **TRAINING**

# 2021-2023 Master in Business Intelligence and Data Analytics

IEBS Business School, Barcelona

2017-2022 Industrial Engineer

Universidad de la Sabana, Chía-Cundinamarca

2023 Certificate Advanced Transact-SOL

The School of SOL

2023 Badge GitHub Universe 2023 Cloud Skills Challenge

Microsoft Learn

**2021 Certificate KAIZEN™ Lean Manufacturing –** Foundations

Universidad de la Sabana-Kaizen Institute, Chía-Cundinamarca